{
    "id": "6f4f92170b084e398847509c8c306b97",
    "title": "Both, Either And Neither Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She has eaten ....................... of the chops.",
            "description": "We use both to refer to two people or things. ",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7184db2bf48b41d3a145fdd9e67ba7e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice sends you ........................ her love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f752e792cf244d36b38b7cc72a49f443"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. of us were ill so we didn't go to work.",
            "description": "Both means this and that. Either means this or that. Neither means not this and not that.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29e2be7e6dbc4285ac89fbe5e4814979"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like ......................... of my Grammar teachers.",
            "description": "Instead of not....both, we use either. ",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4ea2ef2fe534287b43d4ca5ba51fa85"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul and Ravi .......................... went to the party.",
            "description": "Both means this and that.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "927db6670fd94df8b389afae7fea3f33"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... of us play cricket regularly.",
            "description": "Both means this and that.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "27d1667e5b6e4945a8cef212d2979c1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... of us went to the party.",
            "description": "Both expressions are possible here with totally different meanings. Both means this and that. Neither means not this and not that. ",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Neither",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "90aa5b114901403092f0af89a374bd30"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn't choose between them. I liked them ........................",
            "description": "Both means this and that.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bec62d5dad0449b29d343820759d69cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can take ........................... the apple or the orange. You can't have them ......................",
            "description": "Either is used before the first of two alternatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "either, either",
                "either, both",
                "both, either"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d401a7ed368b41b8ae73db4c375ddd51"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think highly of .............................. of them.",
            "description": "Instead of not...both, we use either.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6f0d681d7c8b44be8a83a9cfc7f480fa"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... swim.",
            "description": "We do not normally use both...not. Instead we use neither.",
            "answers": [
                "Both of us cannot",
                "Neither of us can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5db231e58a0e45c28066165647588251"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't want ......................................",
            "description": "Neither is a negative word. We can't use it with not. ",
            "answers": [
                "either chocolate or cake",
                "neither chocolate nor cake",
                "both chocolate and cake"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b0171556922471d835b513070360869"
        }
    ]
}